(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 33)
So Yeon.
Gosh, yes. I'll be right out.
(Planning Director, Cha Seok Jin)
This is new. You don't usually
get off work this early.
Why do you think?
I get it.
You want to have dinner with me
for a change.
I was actually going to be
really upset if we went...
another week without a date.
(Planning Director, Cha Seok Jin)
Do you really not know
what today is?
What day is it?
Never mind.
Come on, what day is it?
How do you forget every year?
Did you really not know
today was my dad's memorial service?
Oh, right.
If I were you, I would at least
write it down somewhere.
I'm sorry.
I'll buy the fruit on the way.
Let's go.
Let me see.
How is it?
You are really good
at cooking, So Yeon.
I'm good at making
everything my husband liked.
Right, a memorial service
is nothing special.
You just prepare the food he liked
when he was alive.
Your husband's spirit
will enjoy the meal.
Really?
Should I add more sesame seeds?
Sesame seeds.
If I had known
it was your father's memorial,
I would've dressed up a bit more.
Should we buy some clothes
on the way?
Don't bother.
Let's hurry.
Ms. Park must be having a hard time
working all alone.
Mom.
Mr. Seok Jin, you're home.
Did you make
a lot of delicious food?
Yes.
- I see you came too.
- Of course.
It's Father's memorial,
so of course I came.
Something smells good.
Ms. Park, what should I do first?
There's no need for you
to do anything.
You don't have to help.
I'll help you out a bit.
The table layout looks
a bit unusual.
Seok Jin said
it's like a birthday party.
Those were
all my husband's favorite foods.
How can a memorial meal
be a birthday meal?
What's this?
Was it Dad's?
I prepared your usual drink.
Thank you, Director Joo.
Around this time every year,
you have trouble sleeping.
Do I?
You usually take sleeping pills
around this time every year,
but I thought a glass of whiskey
would be less harmful than pills.
I suppose so.
Anyway, you're very attentive,
Director Joo.
You even notice
all of those little things.
Of course.
I have spent so many years
by your side,
so I should naturally know.
You say it comes naturally to you,
but why can't my wife see it?
Well then, get some rest.
Are you having fun, Seok Jin?
Yes.
Is that an airplane?
You won't be too late today, right?
Seok Jin has been looking forward
to this play so much.
I'll check out the factory today
and head straight home.
Are you sure? You promised.
Get ready with Seok Jin
and wait for me.
- I'll be home early.
- Okay.
Have a good day, honey.
Mom, when is Dad coming home?
He said he'll be here soon.
Let's wait just a little longer.
Hello.
Is this Cha Seong Woo's residence?
That's right. How can I help you?
You need to come
to the hospital right away.
Your husband has been
in an accident.
What?
(Emergency Medical Center)
Oh no.
Excuse me.
Where can I find Cha Seong Woo?
Please head that way.
Ma'am, you shouldn't see him
like this. Allow us to...
Honey.
Seong Woo.
I'm here.
Wake up, will you?
Honey.
- What do I do?
- Ma'am.
- Honey, wake up.
- Please calm down, ma'am.
- Honey, oh no!
- Ma'am, please calm down.
- Seong Woo, wake up. I'm here.
- Ma'am.
Honey!
- Honey, no!
- Please calm down.
- Honey!
Honey!
No, this can't be!
Honey, no...
Honey...
Honey.
I'm sorry.
Seok Jin.
What are we going to do?
(Cheongma)
Exactly how much
did they inflate the price?
Paintings that normally go
for 2,000 to 5,000 dollars...
seem to have sold for 200,000
to 300,000 dollars each.
Hold on.
Isn't that at least 50 or 60 times
the original price?
There appear to be
off-the-books buyers...
who aren't on the VIP list.
It's likely that they're speculators
tied to the development site.
At this point,
Chairman Kim doesn't just stink.
He's a walking landfill.
Just secure the evidence for now.
If we act rashly right now,
they will just cut their losses
and run.
Sure, I'll stand by for now.
I suppose it's time
for me to make a move.
These are tender tea leaves
that endured the cold winter wind,
so the flavor
is very clear and delicate.
Shall we savor it slowly?
Is this your first time
at the tea house?
I used to just enjoy tea
alone at home,
but I heard about this gathering,
so I gathered the courage to come.
I still have a long way to go
and so much to learn.
Gosh, not at all. Far from it.
From the way you pour the tea
and your breathing,
I can feel
a different level of class.
It's a delightful sight.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Four, nine, two, one.
Is the owner of 4921 here?
Yes, what is this about?
You call that decent parking?
- Right, sorry about that.
- Move it already!
Right, I'm coming.
I'll move it right now.
Let's go.
My phone.
You sure stuffed yourself
with a lot, didn't you?
No wonder your stomach is bursting.
Ma'am.
Have you seen my phone?
No, I didn't see any phone.
Then where did I leave it?
Did you lose your phone, sir?
Gosh, this is bad.
I can't do without my phone.
Unbelievable.
Director Joo's secretary's office
told me to come help you out.
You know who I mean.
The tall and handsome secretary
who was recently hired.
Excuse me.
Thank you for last time.
For what?
You asked the guard
outside the storage room...
to give me a hand.
Oh, that?
I wanted to help you myself,
but I thought it might
make you feel uncomfortable,
so I asked the guard for a favor.
Everything went smoothly
because of your help.
Thank you.
Are you really thankful?
What?
If you're truly thankful,
how about having a meal together?
You see,
I'm still settling in,
so it's a bit awkward to eat alone.
I see.
Eating alone in the cafeteria
feels kind of awkward.
You've been here longer,
so I'd love to join you...
if you don't mind.
Sure thing.
Since lunch hour is almost over,
it's gotten pretty quiet in here.
Right, I suppose it is.
Can I call you my senior?
Of course.
I heard you assist Director Joo.
That's right.
Personally, I've always...
sincerely respected Ms. Joo.
You respect her?
When I was young,
I grew up in an orphanage.
Thanks to the tuition
Ms. Joo sponsored,
I was able to safely graduate
from college.
I see.
Ms. Joo sponsored an orphanage?
Yes.
If it were not for her,
I likely would've
lost my way entirely by now.
Because of my background,
I was looked down upon
a lot everywhere.
So I wandered off the right path
quite a bit.
Back then,
it felt like the entire world
was pushing me away.
That must've been very hard for you.
My situation isn't entirely
the same,
but that feeling of being abandoned
by the whole world?
I can relate to that to some extent.
You know what's funny?
I feel like I open up
so easily around you.
I don't normally talk about myself
this easily around others.
Sometimes a casual relationship
is just easier.
Who knows? It could grow deeper.
As colleagues at work,
we can at least discuss
our worries like this, right?
Yes, of course.
I told you we should just buy some.
Does money grow on trees?
Mr. Park gave us
a ton of young radishes...
he grew in his own garden.
All of this was free.
We could've just sold
those radishes for cash.
They're going to get thrown away
anyway.
You keep quiet.
You rejected all the women
that I set you up with.
No one's going to offer
to set you up anymore.
Why did you even bother?
I need to figure myself out first
before I can date anyone.
Besides, now isn't the time
for me to be dating.
Shut it and give this a taste.
How is it?
Swallowing that
won't exactly kill you, son.
Grandma, taste it yourself.
You really need
to try this yourself.
What?
Hold on.
Are you sure this isn't spoiled?
I can't even understand
what you're saying.
Hold on a second.
I'll bring a real master chef over.
- What?
Hey, where are you going
at this hour?
Then, I'll give it a try.
Mom, is this food waste?
What? Food waste?
Seriously, ma'am?
Here, please try some.
Wow, just the color alone...
That's what I'm talking about.
It just makes you want
a bowl of rice.
Wait, let me get some rice.
Isn't my mom a great cook?
Teun Teun,
growing up with a mom
who's a great cook..
is a real blessing.
Take me, for example.
Man, I'm really jealous of you,
Teun Teun.
Jealous, my foot.
Then why don't you try some?
You're no master chef,
but you're still a pretty good cook.
Mi Rae, have you considered...
opening a boarding house?
A boarding house sounds good.
Eun Guk, give me some rice.
I'd like some.
Chairman Kim, ma'am, you're here.
Ms. Kim.
- Ma'am, please have a seat.
- Thank you.
Thank you for coming all the way
out here. Please have a seat.
By the way, how did you know
to make a reservation here?
When the late chairman was alive,
I used to bring him here often.
I really wanted to bring you...
and your wife back here, sir.
I see.
Her late father
was very down-to-earth.
Rather than fancy and neat places,
he liked simple, warm places
like this.
Yes, that's right.
However, CEO Kang seems to have...
the exact opposite personality
of the late chairman.
Is that so?
A person destined
for great things...
needs to know
how to quietly read the room.
But CEO Kang...
is a bit hasty.
I warn him from time to time,
but he's naturally so impatient...
that my words
just don't get through to him.
It's only because it's me
that I can understand CEO Kang.
At the last gathering,
I was so embarrassed.
I am truly sorry, sir.
I deeply apologize once again.
Please don't.
I didn't mention it
to get an apology from you.
Goodness.
Anyway, for your sake,
I'll make sure to handle
Cheongma's distribution carefully.
Don't worry too much. All right?
I leave it in
your capable hands, sir.
Right.
I met Chairman Kim today.
Really? What did he say?
What do you think?
He said that for my sake,
he'll help out
Cheongma's distribution.
Well, that's a given.
What do you mean it's a given?
Do you know how sincerely
I apologized to him today?
You're always so polite
when it comes to Chairman Kim.
Do you think I'm doing this for fun?
I'm just trying to fix your mess.
Why are you being so twisted?
I went and apologized on your behalf
for the mess you made.
Shouldn't you be thanking me?
You know,
time will tell
who you should truly...
be thankful to.
What's his problem?
Chairman Kim sold
his wife's paintings...
for a hugely inflated price?
The lands Chairman Kim
recently purchased...
seem to have been secured in advance
as locations for the new outlets.
And this is proof...
that Chairman Kim's acquaintances
bought the land?
Yes.
Since Chairman Kim couldn't
buy them directly,
his acquaintances
bought them instead...
and apparently split the profits.
It seems he's still looking into
the clan land in Gisan.
He acted like he was so clean,
but talk about having skeletons
in his closet.
The more we dig,
the bigger the skeletons get.
From the looks of it, an even
bigger deal will take place...
at the upcoming gallery event.
Rather than going
for his throat right now,
it'd be more effective...
to draw our sword
when the time is right.
Right.
Let's wait for the right time.
Yes, this is Joo Mi Ran.
Ae Sook, is that you? It's me.
Why do you keep
calling yourself Mi Ran...
instead of your pretty name,
Ae Sook?
You have the wrong number.
Wrong number?
Do you think I'd forget
my Ae Sook's voice?
I bet you miss me too.
Just hang tight.
I'll find you very soon.
Go find An Guk Cheol right now.
Right. I've already
tracked his movements...
through the PI agency.
Don't make a move yet.
Approach him pretending to help,
and have him dancing
in the palm of your hand.
If you corner him out of nowhere,
there's no telling what he'll do.
Sure, I'll make my move right now.
Jun Hwan.
Yes, Ms. Joo.
I believe it's part of the process.
While trying to clean up my life,
I just happened
to get a little muddy,
and I'm currently
wiping away the dirt.
That's my take on it.
Of course.
Whatever dirt you've got on you,
I'll clean it right off.
Director Joo hired a new secretary?
Yes, it seems she hired
a new executive secretary,
and a pretty young one at that.
Have you met him?
I bumped into him in the hallway.
I was moving
some defective samples at the time,
and he helped me out.
Is that so?
Well, Ms. Joo probably needed
someone young to work with,
someone quicker on their feet.
But it seemed like his background
was quite similar to mine.
In what way?
He grew up facing hardships
in an orphanage.
I heard he even finished
his college studies...
with the scholarship
Ms. Joo sponsored.
That's why he trusts her
and is all the more loyal to her.
His loyalty will be unwavering.
He even called me his senior.
Having someone call me senior...
made me feel a heavy sense
of responsibility.
Of course.
You can't stay the youngest one here
forever, Eun Seol.
Exactly. It's fascinating.
Still,
no matter how similar
your backgrounds are,
don't trust them too much.
That's just
how workplace life works.
Right when you start believing
someone is on your side,
that is exactly
when they stab you in the back.
Things always happen
when you let your guard down.
That's true.
The closer they are,
the more cautious you need to be.
Then I should be the most careful
around you, Attorney Seo.
Me?
You just said
I need to be most careful...
around those closest to me.
The person closest to me is you,
so I should be the most careful
around you.
Well, that's true, but...
Come on, I should be an exception.
That hurts a little.
- I'm only joking.
- Whatever.
Buy me lunch, then.
When will you be done?
We'll be late at this rate.
Let me finish this up.
It's already been 30 minutes.
I know. I'm almost done.
Done.
My parents rarely treat us,
so couldn't you
wrap up work early today?
I'm sorry. Let's get going. Come on.
Let's hurry.
Seriously?
Are Mom and Dad
still stuck in their meeting?
The shareholders' meeting
must be running late.
Seriously,
why can nobody be on time?
Where are your manners?
And you have such great manners?
Of course I do. I'm always on time.
Stop pretending to be busy.
(CEO Kang Young Hoon)
Seok Jin, what do you have there?
What? It's nothing.
Gosh, we're sorry.
Did you wait long?
What took you so long?
We might lose our dinner reservation.
I pushed it back.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
Come on.
Oh my, is someone pouting?
How are the store sales lately?
They're increasing by
about 10 to 20 percent every week.
It might just be the opening effect,
so don't let your guard down.
There are probably plenty
of people around you...
who are hoping that
your initial momentum will die down.
Of course.
I won't let my guard down.
Dad, can we not talk shop
over dinner?
She's right.
Let's just relax during the meal.
Our future son-in-law
is going to get indigestion.
To me, Chief Cha is...
the general manager
of Cheongma's new brand.
Being my future son-in-law
is something to wait and see about.
There you go again.
It's so obvious when you try
to test him, you know.
Who says I'm testing him?
By the way,
I noticed there was a lighter
on your desk, sir.
Oh, that?
That lighter is like
my dad's comfort toy.
He doesn't even smoke,
but he cherishes it.
If you think about it,
it's kind of cute.
Oh, come on. Cute, really?
It's an old habit I can't shake.
That model must have been popular
back in the day.
Actually, a few days ago,
I saw an identical one at my house.
An identical one?
Yes, it was definitely
the same model.
It's a vintage lighter,
so I guess that makes sense.
It must have been a model
that everyone wanted back then.
(A Trap Called Desire)
You know Chairman Min's son,
Min Jae Seong, right?
How about him as a match
for our Hae Ra?
As a match for Hae Ra?
I will dedicate my body and soul
to serve you, Eun Seol.
You've been flirting less lately.
But who knows how liquid courage
will make you flirt?
I'm just scared of everything.
Can the retrial even be held?
Was Manager Na really the killer?
Will you be okay on your own?
Director Joo can accompany me.
I'll prepare the gift
for Chairman Kim.
I'll handle An Guk Cheol on my end.
This is what you call
a perfect crime.
Flawless and perfect.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)